

John Michael

SENIOR FULL STACK ENGINEER

Details

Los Angeles, CA

+1 231 276 1888

beauty.daughter0310@gmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH 1991/04/22

Skills

HTML/CSS

Javascript/Typescript

Node.Js

React.js/Next.js

Vue.js

Web.3/Ethers

Solidity/Truffle

GraphQL

PHP/Laravel

MySQL/Oracle

MongoDB/Firebase

C++/C#/Java

Git/BitBucket

CI/CD

Profile

Highly capable, versatile and accomplished Senior IT Engineer with more than 8 years extensive management experience, planning and implementing. I have indepth knowledge of Information Technology, Finance domain, Decentralized Finance and NFT Marketplaces and participated in Web-software development as Full Stack Engineer.

My career goal is to move into management as a CTO, and I know this role would help me hone my leadership skills.

Employment History

Front End Engineer at Faculty Group

FEBRUARY 2022

- Built Pixel-based modern style FE in OTARIS and SPOOL
- Integrated third-party API such as EMailJS and Web3 in FE
- Used WS/WSS and Fetch APIS to communicate with BE
- Provided high quality and speed of FE creation as intended by the design team
- Customized all components and integrated smooth transition and animations
- Deployment : https://otaris.io, https://www.spool.fi/, https://www.app.spool.fi/

Back End Engineer at ASUENE Co., Ltd, Shinagawa, Japan

OCTOBER 2021 - JULY 2022

- Arranged Front-End UI elements with Vuetify and customized theme upon it.
- Integrated third-party APIS using Laravel
- Managed GCP, GCS and auto-run batch using Laravel
- Database design
- Analyzed and displayed statistics data using D3
- Built docker environment, implemented Nginx, Redis
- Built CI/CD pipelines on GitHub for Test and Deploy
- Deployment: https://earthene.com

Full Stack Engineer at Lead Edge Consulting Co., Ltd, Tokyo, Japan

JANUARY 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

- Developed NFT Market place able to integrate with opensea.io
- Collection based Mint System(Lazy Mint for Zero gas fee) base on ERC721
- IPFS storage for content upload and implemented Firebase
- Built out a new version of front-end application using NextJS
- Implemented event monitoring on Web3.js
- Multi-chain integration (Ethereum, Polygon)
- Introduced Staking, Liquidity Pool, NFT market place
- Built CI/CD Pipelines on GitHub for Test and Deploy
- Deployment: https://leadedge-c.com/

Full Stack Engineer at Shogan Technology Co., Ltd., Toronto,

Canada

FEBRUARY 2018 - DECEMBER 2020

- Ensured a well-architecture platform using React, Typescript
- Arranged UI with TailwindCSS and Ant Design
- Optimized the codebase converting class components to functional component using React Hooks, Redux, Context, resulting in the size of the codebase of 90%

GCP/AWS	
Languages	
English	

Creative Problem Solving

Leadership Skills

Japanese

Chinese

- Improved code quality using ESLint, Prettify and Git Hooks
- Deployment: https://getshogun.com/frontend

C#, PHP, AIR Engineer at KOKUYO Co., LTD, Nagoya, Japan

JANUARE 2016 - FEBURUARY 2017

- Role as Disassembly engineer to decompile previous versioned file
- Programmed UI, file version manage, Undo/Redo manage with AIR
- Programmed custom IME control using C#
- Design Database and make Restful API for Front-End

C# Engineer at SilverStarJapan Co., Ltd, Gifu, Japan

APRIL 2012 - AUGUST 2015

- Role as engineer in developing ItiAwasePro series
- Arrange UI with Ribbon UI component, C#
- Made Undo/Redo data structure and algorithms
- Implemented Scanner and Printer mechanism into C# component
- Implemented Tab Interface and Spreadsheet into ItiAwasePro5
- Role as CTO in ItiAwasePro6, 7, 8
- Programmed detail test cases using C#Unit

Education

Bachelor of Information Science, Tokyo University

SEPTEMBR 2008 - FEBRUARY 2012

Department of Information Science, Faculty of Science